the model providers. So this is OpenAI
Anthropic and probably Google eventually
are kind of coming for everything,
right? There's this uh notion that if
you build a company that's just a wrap
around one of these models that the
model providers are going to eventually
come and like eat your company, right?
They're going to come and like take take
over.
>> Best part of Viking when you can just,
you know, critical think, right?
Yeah, dude.
>> Hey, what's up guys? Before we get into
the show, I wanted to mention something
super quick from our friends at Threat
Locker. And I actually think you are
going to think it's pretty awesome
because so much of Bug Bounty is often,
you know, kind of quoted as like, "Yeah,
but hackers will never exploit that
because they can just get in via
fishing." Well, that's actually true.
You know, most of the time whenever
companies get breached, it's because of
fishing or access to that user's account
or, you know, they do something like do
a whole bunch of push notification to FA
and eventually a user gets so much
fatigue they approve it. But they have a
solution for this. Threadlocker has a
thing called zero trust cloud access,
right? Which prevents access to cloud
resources or SAS resources based on the
device you're logging in from. So if a
user gets fished, right, they put in
their credential, like they get fished
or they get fished, they the attacker
has the credentials, maybe they even
have a way to get the MFA because they
did some sort of SIM swap because they
have a hookup at Verizon or AT&T or
whatever, right? So they have the
credentials, they have the MFA, they
still can't get in because the zero
trust cloud access like will basically
straight up allow or deny people access
to resources based on the device you're
logging in from. So, if you're an
enterprise or a company and you're
concerned about the highest risk, which
really is fishing, this is a way to add
another like basically impenetrable
layer to preventing it and securing your
network. Um, yeah, back to the show.
Hey, what's up guys? Before we jump in
the episode, I want to mention one more
thing. All of the discussion over this
past weekend uh made me think it might
be useful to add a little bit of
clarification just because it feels like
there's so much nuance being lost in the
world around the debate of AI and its
impact on bug bounty. So in this episode
we talk about a lot of effects on bug
bounty that AI is having and that it
will continue to have kind of going
forward. And I would say it's like 60 or
70% kind of like on the negative side of
just like things that could impact the
industry or us as hunters negatively.
And we're here to bring you the truth.
Like I'm going to do that. Like that's
what we're here for. But I did want to
add a little bit of nuance. When I say
or when anyone on the podcast is talking
about like things being over or Bug
Bounty's dead, it really is uh hyperbole
to bring emphasis on the problem, right?
or on the potential problems that are
coming. In my opinion, I think this is
going to be the biggest year ever for
Bug Bounty. And I even mentioned this on
my on my blog. Um, but that's not to say
that there are a lot of things kind of
going downhill, which we'll mention in
the episode. And so, I wanted to add
this here as a little bit of context so
that no one thinks I'm like, you know,
quitting Bug Bounty or that I think
anyone should like give up on it or that
the industry is over. You know, I think
those types of hyperboles are really to
shout out and show um to bring awareness
towards the types of things that are
happening which are going to change our
industry tremendously and it has the
potential to go bad. And so I do think
that we wanted to highlight that and get
your all's opinion on how it could be
done better which we'll talk about here
in just a second.
>> Dude, what's up?
>> How's it going man? It's been a while
since we last done an episode.
>> That's true. We got to cover for Justin
and some medical stuff.
>> Yeah, absolutely. But I think it's been
overdue. I'm looking forward to it.
>> Yeah, dude. We've got a pretty uh
controversial episode. Uh I do want to
say off the bat cuz there are people
with uh feelings on both sides of the
fence that we're going to be discussing
the the thoughts that either Bug Bounty
is dead or we're just getting started.
But uh even if that's not your cup of
tea, stick around. We've got um a
request for feedback basically and I'm
gonna go ahead and tell it up front but
uh it's forms.ctb.show
futureofbugbounty
and that's underscoreepparated. We
really really really I think need
feedback and I think we're going to pass
that feedback along to the platforms
because I think there is a lot of
different network effects on the bug
bounty industry and I personally am a
little bit worried about it. My my
wife's personally worried about it too.
Um but yeah so
>> yeah no we we'll get into the weeds of
it but it was a discussion which started
on the CTS to address some of the
problems we've been having and then
since that discussion happened it just
seems that there was like a 3-day block
of just stuff dropping the entirety of
this week. So, we thought it would be
good to capture other people's thoughts
and opinions as well outside the CTS and
see what everyone thought.
>> Yeah. When he says CTers, there's
basically a tier in the Discord for
critical thinkers that we abbreviate to
CT a lot of times. Um, and so that's
people who have, you know, subscribed
and there's a lot of really good
discussions that happen there if you
want to hop in. But, um, yeah, this past
week has been, I feel like, a really big
newssheavy week that plays a lot into
this discussion. Um, did you have any
other like kind of off-topic stuff or
just like random news items or things
that are going on in your life that you
wanted to mention?
>> No. Um, I think
>> How's hunting going?
>> Yeah. Um, yeah, I've been spending
more time on tooling. Um, a lot more
time on tooling. I'd done a three live
event stint back toback. One of them
over overlapped and I was like, I was
fried. I spoke to you about it, but I
was just like completely dead from that.
It was very intense. And throughout
that, I kept going, "Okay, I'll improve
some tooling. I'll I'll update this
skill or I I'll make that change." And
my list just stacked up bigger than me.
And now I'm slowly working through the
list of backlog. And obviously, I've got
company stuff, accounting, so I'm very
much catching up, but I'm just coming
out of the end and now doing some
tooling before I jump into my next event
next week. excited,
>> dude. Insane.
>> Are you in a Are you in an event right
now?
>> Yeah, the Lisbon event. I'm doing it
remotely. Um,
>> nice.
>> It's been fine. You know, plenty of
findings. I think that a lot of the
discussion we're going to have, I think,
play plays into it. So, actually, we can
use that as a good segue. I I I think
they had a shorter dupe window, which I
think is really smart. I think events
these days need a shorter dupe window
with everyone using hacking agents. I
think that people are finding bugs much
faster, especially that kind of I hate
calling it low hanging fruit because
it's more like mediumhanging fruit,
right? I kind of use that phrase. And
so, but that medium hanging fruit really
is getting kind of like slurped up by
everybody's models all at the same time.
And so, I think there's like some
massive dupe splits. Um, and anyways,
yeah, so I think that, you know, that's
kind of one of the network effects at
play. But um the the thing that has
really triggered this discussion more
than anything else were kind of two news
items. We can talk about them
independently before we get into the
discussion about whether you know Bug
Bunny's dying, but I think the first one
is Google's bounty range. Did you see
that?
>> Yeah. Um I saw it drop and
the way it dropped with all the
discussions we've been having to see
tiers, I was just like I didn't need to
see this right now. But let's get into
it because the Google VRP essentially
dropped their bounties, right? Um
or changed some bounty ranges, which
also
>> Yeah, I do think that it's kind of a
simplification to say they dropped them.
I saw a lot of people basically implying
it was all bad news. does kind of seem
like at least for the like really
impactful bugs, which, you know, there's
only a handful of them and only a few
people in the world that could even find
them, those bounty ranges went up, you
know, but then the other ones kind of
dropped like I don't I think did did
they say they're not paying for lows and
mediums or something along those lines.
>> Uh yeah, it looks like it on certain
scope in the VRP. Not the entire not the
entire scope, just to be clear, but
certain aspects in their bounty program.
Android and Chrome, right, are the main
ones.
>> Android and Chrome. Should we share this
actually for people watching?
>> Sure. They basically have a blog post.
I'll let Brandon share it, but it's
called Evolving the Android and Chrome
BRPs. And I mean, you can't really blame
them, right? I think they're getting
spammed with tons of reports.
>> Mhm. Yeah. And if you speak to program
managers or speak to anyone's other
platforms, it's very much a massive pain
point right now. Some of the stats speak
for themselves. And I think if you've
got any open reports, you'll definitely
feel this thing because man, stuff is
just taking forever. Like the old life
cycle of like, okay,
>> I probably know this is going to be like
a 4 week payout maybe is just completely
gone out the window for the time being.
Um, whilst programs are dealing with a
massive massive influx of reports. Um,
and learning how to deal with that
because I think it's only going to
increase now as time goes on. Um, so it
kind of makes sense. It kind of falls
into that. But Google, the good, okay,
let's just start off on this. The good
news is there are reward increases for
more impactful bugs. So that isn't good.
Like up to 1.5 mil for a zero click full
chain on Pixel Titan M2
with persistence. So, it's not all bad,
but there is obviously downstream
effects of modifying your bounty tables
with some of the quantity you're going
to get in and some of the quality as
well.
>> Yeah, definitely. Um, and then yeah, so
I think that uh there's also another uh
screenshot that I saw going around. It's
not in this blog post, but that the um
some of the vulnerabilities that you
know many people would even consider
mediums and highs across these um brps
pay way less. Like I saw one that it's
like a a bug that would have paid
thousands of dollars before now pays
like 500 bucks. Um I don't know if you
saw that one going around.
>> No. No. Have you got that?
>> Yeah. Let me see if I can find it really
quickly.
>> Yeah, no worries.
And yeah, here we can see some of the
key changes to the VRP. They're
incentivizing uh actionable reports.
Um AI has obviously made report writing
easier for I would say all of us in some
respects. Um but it also means that
they're expecting higher quality reports
and more actionable reports, which I
think is fair enough. Um they're phasing
out some of their bonuses. Um,
and basically just having a bit of a
revamp of the program. So, if you hack
Google or are thinking of hacking Google
on some of the Android and devices,
um, definitely check out this blog post
before you get into it and update
yourself because it is fundamentally
changing the the ecosystem.
>> Yeah, I can't find it. It's fine. If we
find it, we'll wind up throwing the show
notes.
Um, you know, this plays into again the
whole meta discussion that was really
kicked off, I think, also by Anthropic
rolling out their security review to
more users. So, Anthropic had like a
security review thing in the past. And I
think people have known that Anthropic
was kind of continuing to care more
about the cyber security abilities of
their models because they just like made
such a leaprog right back when 46
dropped. And I think that this uh you
know really along with everything else
that we've been discussing kind of it
doesn't scare me but I think it's just
like we're we're definitely moving from
a previous phase of Bug Bounty into like
a completely new era. And you know we're
going to go ahead and mention all of
like the quote unquote bad things or all
of the reasons why it's over before the
reasons why we're so back. Um because I
do think a lot of people were upset with
my tweet. So, I quote tweeted anthropic
tweet and basically said it's over when
they released the security thing and and
a lot of people were like it's not over
blah blah blah blah. You know, there's
like lots of trolls that come out of the
woodworks to to argue. Um, but I don't
know if they have the the full picture.
So, I I want to paint the full picture.
I think these are the network effects
that um worry me and then we'll talk
about the network effects like all all
of the upside, right? And so so we can
go through these one at a time and I
want your like feedback on each of these
and you tell me like how how true you
think it is.
>> Okay.
>> So the first one is
>> there are so many reports that these
platforms and programs can't really keep
up right and so this is driving some
programs to shut down some programs to
stop accepting lows or mediums like
Google did there and then all of the
programs are delayed in triage times and
payment times.
Yeah, I mean I don't think you can
really argue with that if you're an
active hunter and you've been keeping an
eye on some of the notifications
programs have been bringing out um how
regularly you're getting paid and how
things are getting triaged. I think
that's completely undeniable. And one of
the platforms, I can't remember which,
uh, dropped a statistic of the like the
trend of traffic increases, which I saw
in a tweet tweet as well, and it was
something like 80% up of like compared
from this time last year or something
like that.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. It's insane, right? Wasn't there a
thing that said like Hacker One gets
like 200 reports a minute or something
crazy?
>> Yeah. I I mean I'm not sure if that is
like valid reports or like total report
count but it's still a crazy number.
>> Crazy. Okay, so here's the next one.
Models. One thing that I hear all the
time as like push back is like yeah but
like humans are still more skilled. So
even if you know these these uh these
agents find like the lower hanging
fruit, we'll definitely always need
humans for that like higher quality
vulnerabilities, right? In some sense, I
do think that's true, but based on the
bugs that my hacking agent finds, like
many of them are so skilled, I wouldn't
have found them. And many of them are
exactly like the things I find. And
we're like in this situation where, you
know, I always bring up Cyberbench
because it's like the only full like
kind of production level eval, but you
know, the Cyberbench score went from
like 30 something% to 60 something% with
46 and 47. And do we think that's going
to like get worse? It's not right. These
models are going to continue to improve.
>> I don't want to take us on a on a side
path now. I'm wondering if we should get
into your whole debate
>> about what you think around like
privacy.
>> Well, so here just here's the thing on
that though. Models will continue to
improve I think overall. But
>> yeah,
>> to contradict that Opus 47, what on
earth? Like I really was not a fan of
that. Did Did you switch over or have
you used it? What did you think?
>> As far as I can tell, I have some
indications that it's slightly worse and
other indications that it's about the
same. It's really hard to tell for me
personally. I know a lot of people have
disliked it, but
>> yeah. And
it's there's so many nuances here as
well because like we also had the debate
a couple of weeks back when I was like,
dude, is your clawude like severely
nerfed? Because mine is just it's making
more work for me right now. So I think
although actual models at their base
will become better and the latest round
of the open source models that we had
dropped last week definitely proves
that. Like if you look at some of the
benchmarks from these smaller 27 billion
models and 30 whatever billion models
insane. They pack a punch for their
size. But
the taxonomy around it is model
providers obviously have to scale
traffic properly. If they're doing new
R&D or releasing a new model or
whatever, they have to ensure that they
have enough compute to do that. So as a
consumer, we're in this spot where we
just randomly get throttled and we're
sort of at the mercy of that which I
really don't like. So overall, yes, I
would say models are getting better, but
there's obviously a lot of nuances
around the economy of that as well.
Yeah. So I think um well like actually
let's get into we're going to table
that. So we're going to argue after this
discussion on whether it's over or we're
you know we're still early. Um me and
Brandon are going to have a little
debate around um model providers and
training data and this sort of thing. Uh
>> Mhm.
>> because I want to like clearly lay out
all these network effects. So I'm also
going to summarize. So the first one is
that the network's effects on whether
bug bounty is over is one. There's so
many reports that the programs platforms
can't keep up. That's point one, right?
And under that is that they're some are
closing, some are like reducing what
they accept and they're all delayed. The
next one is these models keep getting
better, right? The other thing I would
say is that the model providers, so this
is open AI and anthropic and probably
Google eventually are kind of coming for
everything, right? there's this uh
notion that
if you build a company that's just a
wraparound one of these models that the
model providers are going to eventually
come and like eat your company, right?
They're going to come and like take take
over. And I think that that is um
sometimes overblown and other times I
think it's like extremely relevant. And
in this case, I think it's extremely
relevant because security is so
important. And you know, in the past, it
has been hard, but now,
dare I say it's easy. Like I I I really
think
the effort I have to put in to find bugs
is definitely far less. Right? I'm not
necessarily saying it's easy. I do think
that you have to be still be highly
skilled to vet false positives from true
positives. Actually, let's add that to
theopium copium section down here below.
Um, still lots of false positives. So,
we're going to get down to that in a
second, but I think that the model
providers are coming for security
because one, they need to to make sure
that their networks to make sure that
their infrastructure is secure and
there's some level of money in it. It's
not actually it's not actually that big
relative to some other industries like
shopping or whatever, but uh or
advertising, right? Like the security um
industry at large is not as big as some
others that they could go after. But I
do think that it's also important to
them and then it's also important to
humanity, right, that we like continue
to keep things secure. Um, and so and so
I think that they're coming after that.
The next thing is we have so many
startups that are basically coming out
to do automation pin like pin testing.
Like of course there are the expose of
the world that have been around as their
main gig, but every other company's
getting into it. Like Sneak is building
one. Whiz is building one.
>> I'm pretty sure the bug bounty programs
are building them. like the bug bounty
platforms.
>> Yeah. And it's I feel like this is a
continuation but a buffed continuation
of like the cycles we see in security.
Like if you go back I don't know maybe 5
years ago it was ASM ASM ASM new ASM
platform attack surface management
attack surface management. Now the next
thing of that is okay agentic pen
testing and you actually uh tweeted I
think it was this week uh quote tweeting
someone's like prices for a pen test and
you're like it's a race to the bottom
now.
>> Yeah.
>> And I feel like that's so true because
>> it to your earlier point it hasn't ever
been easier to do this. It's very
powerful now that we can make a tool do
some form of test. I'm not going to say
if it anyone and say yeah um yeah I'm
not going to do that but
>> it's now easier than before to do that
wrap it up in the service and sell it. I
think the thing is understanding if it's
actually effective and actually good or
not but to your point it it does kind of
feel like a race to the bottom in that
sense because it's become so common.
Everyone's doing it. Oh, lower prices.
Get a full pen test for $100 by our
agentic agent. And you're like, okay,
sounds great, but like what are the
actual results of that? What's how
effective is it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. And and I think like you and
no one would probably argue that it's
going to be better than your kind of mom
and pop pentest shop that does a twoe
engagement with one pentester who
doesn't keep up with the industry and
has no incentivization to work hard
because they're mostly going for a
compliance check mark, right? Like even
if it's a lower quality agentic pin
test, I bet it's still going to be
better than those old ones, you know,
like the the the for compliance just for
the check mark like sock 2 pin test and
so things are still going to get more
secure even bad agentic pin tests are
still better than like check mark pin
tests from the past and so I think
things are going to get more secure and
I think that's really good for humanity
but I do think that all of these layers
of like Yeah. So let me let me go ahead
and mention two two other points uh so
we can like list all the things that are
over that like make me feel like it's
over. One is internal
companies now internal red teams can now
run hack bots on their production
software before it goes external facing
right
>> and on top of that these agents are like
really good at open source code review
and so they can run that internally. So
they're able to run like white box and
blackbox hack bots or security review on
production apps before they come out,
right? Then they can also get automated
pentest from third parties, whether it's
from the bug money platforms or whether
it's from companies like Expo or
whatever. So by the time it gets to us,
the amount of bugs that are there is
going to be so low. And I'm not and I,
you know, I still think that we'll be
able to find vulnerabilities. I think
that, you know, top bug talent is still
the most talented group of individuals
for finding vulnerabilities. And now we
are all even more leveled up. But my
point is that I think that the total
industry and the money that went into it
and like my earnings and your earnings
like it's a mix of low hanging fruit and
then like really complex bugs, right?
>> And a lot of people made their living or
at least made um like they you know made
way more money because of a lot of that
low hanging fruit, right? you get a new
private program invite, you go in there,
you farm it, you feel great about
yourself,
>> and then, you know, then you work really
hard during live hacking events on these
hardened targets to find like these deep
bugs. And it's a mix of all of that. And
and I think that like the the former is
going to be going away, whereas the
latter might last a little bit longer.
>> Yeah. And it feeds into our earlier
point of I think the economy of bug
bounty as we know it is definitely like
dead or slashch changing in terms of
>> it's going through a transition phase
with all these toolings and things like
that and having spoke to some program
managers and some other programs in the
industry
pe they are taking their reports or
taking report this is programs by By the
way, I'm not talking about platforms to
be specific programs. Some programs are
using our reports as expected to develop
their own tooling and AI tooling to help
detect some of these problems that they
keep seeing and keep arising. So that's
definitely happening
>> for some programs I've spoken.
>> When we submit it, it becomes their
intellectual property. So they can use
it the programs, not the platforms.
Yeah,
>> exactly.
>> So it the the TLDDR is like the bars
raising, right? like we've leveled up,
but also it's works both ways.
>> Yeah. My final point here before I recap
all of them for why it's over is that
top hackers like me and like you are now
much much more effective, right? And so
yeah, that bodess well for me and you,
you know, maybe today, maybe for six
months, maybe for a year, but I think
long term that that fact that the
highest skill people can now scale their
knowledge and their expertise across
many more
um scope items. I didn't know whether to
say programs or subdomains or whatever,
but can now scale their knowledge across
many more applications
means that there's going to be less for
everyone else, right? And so, um, I'll
recap now. So, here's here's my claim
for why it's over. There's so many
reports the companies are beginning
programs are beginning to close or not
accept low and mediums or we have super
delayed times and triage and payments
which um adversely affects full-time
hunters like you and I, right? Because
it's like how do we know that we're
going to be able to meet our bills next
month or what have you, right? model
providers are offering uh are now
offering like coderview based services
and I think eventually we'll get to
offering hack bots. The models will keep
getting better and so that delta between
like the human plus AI skill gap and the
AI only will continue to remove because
it's getting closer and closer to our
skill level. Startups are now doing
pentest for cheaper and cheaper. So
companies can now like, you know, buy a
$500 pin test or $1,500 pin test before
it goes into their bug bounty scope or
they can just, you know, stop doing bug
bounty. Internal devs at those companies
and internal red teams can use their
agents to test both their white box and
blackbox reviews or um code. The
platforms are eventually going to be
doing agentic content test on it before
it gets our scope. And then if you get
past all that, now it's in scope. You're
competing with top hackers like me and
like you who are going to be running a
bunch of highskll, highly developed AI
hack bots at scale all the time.
>> Mhm. Yeah. I mean
I mean when you wrap it up like that, it
doesn't sound great, does it?
>> It doesn't sound great, does it? And I
only say this because like I feel like
there are some things like one, I think
that there is also some or copium that
we'll mention in a minute. I also think
there are things that we can do to do
better. I think there are also things
that platforms can do to do better. And
I want to talk about all that, but we
also want your ideas. I know I mentioned
this at the beginning, I want to mention
it again. We're gonna have a forum up.
That's forums.ctb.show
future_of_bug_bounty.
And I we would I would love to hear more
ideas or thoughts about this like why am
I wrong or how can we fix this or how
can we iterate on this? Um so yeah.
>> So I guess let's dive a little deeper in
there. So I guess the overall problem is
that there is an increased amount of
like quantity of reports right now in
the CTS there were initial ideas and
there was actually a tweet from I think
it was a CTO from hacking proof which is
a web free security like bug bounty
platform um and they implemented like a
I don't know what you'd call it like a
submission fee a pledger I don't know um
for each report that you put in. Let me
share my screen because it's quite an
interesting tweet.
Can you see that?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Um, cool. So, they're implementing a fee
per report that basically says, look, if
you want to report, you have to pay this
fee, but you'll get it back at some
point. Providing a report is valid. So,
what's interesting is $1 wasn't enough
skin in the game to like properly
implement it. people just didn't really
care. Sprayed and prayed. $5
>> 80% drop in AI slop and low quality
submissions at $10 a max. And I thought
it was quite an interesting tweet
because
>> programs and platforms have a very real
problem that they need to address and
that is now filtering the noise and
actually getting those valuable findings
that some people are producing in front
of their triage teams and their internal
team so they can fix it. I thought this
was a really interesting concept. Um, I
don't know how I feel about it is what I
would say. I think it's interesting.
>> I think it's genius. I mean, I think
that you once get in the game um because
it means that the bug hunters are going
to be much more skeptical of what
they're about to report and it will save
a ton of
>> of time on the back end. I think this is
like maybe something we need to apply at
scale. I'm sure you saw the GitHub
hack/GitHub uptime issues. Basically,
GhostTy,
uh, the maker of GhostTy, the really
nice terminal, uh, is coming off is like
moving all their code off GitHub because
of GitHub's downtime and stuff. But if
you look at like the number of projects
on GitHub, it's like a straight line up
because of Vibe Coding. Every everyone's
releasing stuff and people who weren't
devs before, like their agents are
telling them to like get stuff on
GitHub. And so it's like it kind of
makes sense. They've had a hard time
keeping up. I mean, agents can push like
>> constant commits like uh mine and JD's
bug bounty uh hackbot
>> uh it pushes every finding to GitHub,
right? And so it's like and every lead
and every note as a as a separate
commit. And so it's like you can imagine
why they're struggling to keep up with
this volume. And so like what if they
charged you
>> I don't know a dollar a month for a like
per repo,
>> you know? It's like
>> Yeah. No, it it would definitely be
effective to combat because it would
fundamentally change user behavior,
right? If you are just
>> create, oh, I just create this, push it
up, and forget about just in case I need
it, you'll probably go, actually,
>> I just got a USB laying around. I could
just do that instead. Um, but some of
the points raised in the channel, I
can't remember who raised them, was the
point around the economy of that, right?
Obviously
different regions say I don't know for
like Netflix subs for example they scale
that appropriately
>> so that would have to come into
consideration I think.
>> Yeah I think they would have to do that.
Yeah I mean cuz like five bucks to
somebody in India who's getting started
in bug bounty they like probably would
never want to do that.
>> Exactly. But it's very interesting. But
at five, like
I say I'm conflicted because there's two
sides to it. But overall, if I had to
pay $5 per bug, which meant faster
triage, it got handled properly and it
reduced the amount of like slop, which
meant your overall triage experience
would be better. I would take that for
sure.
>> I just don't know how it would scale
across the community and things like
that. I'd be interested to hear people's
thoughts.
>> Yeah, hack and proof has a really big
benefit of being on chain
>> cuz like on submission people can
literally just like add $5 in gas from
it like like of of Ethereum, right? And
so it's like it's like super easy for
them to manage that or whatever. Whereas
it's like
>> on Hacker One, it's going to be kind of
weird like is it going to come out of a
future payment? Are you going to like
PayPal them or Venmo? It's like it feels
like a lot harder to implement, right?
>> Yeah. And there was a concept as well
that someone else mentioned to like put
the monetary things aside of having a
concept of tokens which essentially
acted as money. So say if you get x
amount of valid reports that are triaged
you get a certain amount of tokens you
can report with and then if you get to a
certain signal or rep that gets entirely
removed and then you can report and
things like that. But again,
I don't like I'm saying this because
there are ideas that hold weight, but I
don't know. I can't figure out what the
best approach would be to scale across
platforms, which would lead to the best
outcome for hackers and for the program
and for the platform as well.
>> Yeah. The biggest issue I think with uh
anything like that is like kind of the
same issue that programs have with like
banning people. It's like so are these
people who can't afford it or who are
banned like what are they supposed to do
with the vulnerabilities they find? Just
yolo them on the internet, right? Or
proxy them through other people or
whatever. It's like there are issues
there. But let's let's jump on this uh
copium train where we're talking about
the opposite instead of it being over. I
think here's like the reasons to be
optimistic about it.
So before we move on, do we cover the
data policy usage before we get to that
or not?
>> No, it's more negative stuff. Let's go
let's go positive.
>> Okay. All right. Go. Let's go positive.
>> And I and I feel like it can be, you
know, people are still going to like
hearken it back and understand like
they're going to place I think our
debate in a second into context of that
of that first half. But yeah, now let's
talk about the good stuff. So I saw who
was it?
Hackluke. you know, and it's a lot of
other people have said it before, but
there's just no better time to learn
something than today. Um, and JD
mentioned that too. I think like, you
know, excess doctor wanted to like learn
has been like wanting to learn like to
go deeper in his like front-end client
side attacks and he'll just literally
tell Claude code like, "Hey, spin me up
a lab where I can exploit this. No, it's
not working. Do this right." And now now
teach it to me, you know, and like kind
of like walk yourself through. I don't
know how many people have that much
discipline. It feels like probably
pretty few. Um cuz cuz you and I, you
know, as bug hunters, we always have
this pull on our time where it's like we
could just be doing more bug hunting or
improving our automation or I don't
know, spending time that doing something
that we actually like love, you know,
something leisurely. So I think it is
like hard to u make the time to do that.
But you know, if I was early in my
career, of course, and I was learning, I
feel like there is this huge upside to
learning with LLMs, right?
>> Uh 100%. I actually gave a talk at my
old school um a couple of months back
where I was trying to drill this concept
into the kids because I was like look AI
can give you the answers but use it as a
sparring partner. Don't ask for the
answer directly like use it to learn and
you'll be much more effective and it'll
pay dividends
further down the line. Um, and also
Daniel Measler drops a blog post a while
back which I just love the concept
because it captures it so perfectly and
it's don't take your robots to the gym.
And it's like exactly the same where
>> be disciplined enough to understand when
and when to apply because obviously you
go to the gym for the benefits of going
to the gym. There's no point of like
offloading that to someone else.
So yeah, I really
argument and I've definitely used it to
improve and study a little bit on my
side as well back some of the mobile
stuff I done towards the end of last
year after an event as well.
>> Yeah, I saw a quote tweet by Andre
Kaparthy uh from Yine. Um he says, "You
can't outsource or sorry, you can
outsource your thinking but you cannot
outsource your understanding."
Basically,
>> if you want to outsource your thinking,
but don't outsource your understanding,
right? I think this is something that
Justin's really, really passionate about
that he's saying all the time. It's
like, you know, it's fine to automate
bits of the hacking thing, but you still
need to understand what's happening and
how to do it. So,
>> 100%.
>> So, yeah. So, I think that we're early
in that regard. I mean, um, we humans
have never been more empowered to go and
do anything in the world. Just before we
hopped on the call, I just shared like
three side projects I've built with you
in the last like two weeks.
because of the power of these coding
agents, right? And um and I think the
second big thing is that
the scope is actually big enough across
these big anchor programs that no one
could actually even test it all.
>> Like let's imagine let's imagine our
doom scenario, right? a company like
Yahoo is trying to test stuff internally
and then it gets out and they hire or
like before they push it to the new
scope they like have the bug bounty
platform that they're hosted on do like
an agentic red teaming of like you know
that asset or that scope or whatever and
then it goes it goes live and then you
know whatever they hire expo to do it. I
I think that like the the amount of work
to test like tens of thousands or
hundreds of thousands of subdomains
deeply is actually too much for even the
combination of the internal red team and
the platform agentic part and and a
third party, right? And there so there's
still going to be plenty of
vulnerabilities I think that kind of
like come out due to the large scale of
large companies.
>> Yeah. And it feeds into the next thing
we discussed as well is the fact that
you combine that and then you combine a
team which has adopted AI for
development. You combine those two and
the rate that people can push things
out, new functionality, new features,
it's just like it's insanely quick now.
And I've actually spoken to I can't say
names but programs which have said like
yeah on one side we have got the AI tool
and it helps us and things like that but
the scale of which we're pushing things
out now and the requirement that is
built that we can develop so fast um in
terms of our development life cycles
have shortened that functionality is
being made quicker and pushed out
quicker before we actually have time to
properly vet and fix things.
So I would almost definitely say like
yeah the scopes there and also to
combine with that
the functionality being developed on top
of that scope is a multiplier as well.
>> Yeah and I think that rate is going to
continue to increase obviously like we
stay on top of tech where like we're
implementing that and like using coding
agents a lot. I think you know when you
look at the stats of like the amount of
people that have been like leveled up by
using coding agents at work especially
like these large enterprises
I think it's something like 50% are
using AI but like a lot of that usage is
like one off or like asking about the
code not actually implementing it. I
think that like the way in which AI has
allowed me to you know vibe code at like
10 or 100x the amount of output that I
used to be able to put out. I think that
when these enterprise companies are then
moving at that same rate, like imagine
10,000 software engineers now being like
putting out 50 times more code, right?
Like just the amount the volume of
required testing is then like gigantic,
right? It's like unfathomably large. And
so I think that that really is some
hopeium.
>> Yeah. Cuz like imagine just imagine your
scenario right there and then working in
the apps team having to deal
>> try to review that.
>> Oh man. You'll just be like, "Claude,
find all VS and please report back."
>> Yeah. All right. And and I'm gonna
mention this and I'm gonna give a shout
out to Joel um the former podcast host
of this podcast with Justin help helped
found it. technogeeek. He mentioned to
me I was, you know, saying it's over,
talking about some Hackbot stuff like
maybe two months ago or something and
I've already mentioned this on the pod
once, but and he kind and like he said
something like, you know, like what
percentage of the bugs that come out of
your Hackbot system are valid and I was
like, ah, man, it's such a it's it's
such an astute observation, right?
because it feels to me like I'm getting
a bunch of these free bugs, but I'm like
just choosing not to submit a bunch of
things that aren't actually real
findings, whether they're not critical
enough or whether the um the actual like
uh data that is exposed is like not is
it supposed to be public or there's like
a misunderstanding or it's like a gadget
and not a full bug. So I think like um
when going through this discussion, it
may be easier than ever before to find
stuff, but the people who are finding
stuff might not actually be able to
differentiate between real bugs and
things that are not impactful. And I
think they're very quickly going to be
kind of like uh they're going to very
quickly maybe give up or be demotivated
or feel like that AI can only produce
slop because like they literally don't
have the skills to validate whether it's
true or not. And so then they end up,
you know, stopping hunting or stop
submitting or getting kicked out of
programs because they're submitting so
much junk, right?
>> Yeah. Well, and I think this is exactly
what's happening from everything we just
spoke about, right? The stats, the
amount of submissions now that platforms
and programs having to deal with. I
think that's very real for sure.
Uh, and what was the I've completely
lost track of where we are in this list.
What was the last We had one more Hopian
point, didn't we?
>> Oh, we do. I think I think that's it. I
think that there are,
you know, maybe
Oh, I was going to say this. Yeah. Yeah.
Sorry. There is one big hoping point.
One is that like with the power of these
current like kind of hacking agents,
current hunters have this massive
advantage that they can apply those bugs
at scale and apply their expertise at
scale more than ever before. So even
even given all of that stuff that like
you know makes me makes us think that
it's so over I think that
um there's like a balancing factor here
of we're all going to be much more
effective
>> both at scale because you can like when
you find something you say hey go hunt
for these other places but then in in
efficacy as well. So like let's say you
find some like hidden gem of scope that
like other people haven't got access to.
You are not going to get in there and
find three bugs like you used to. You're
going to get in there and find 10 bugs
and some of them are going to be more
critical than ever, right? Because now
you are I think a lot of times we're all
allocating our time and effort, right?
In the past you get access to some
scope, you have like six or seven hours,
then the next day you get a new invite
or a buddy messages you or whatever. You
pivot off of that, right? So what you
got done in that seven hours might be
all that you do on that scope, right?
Because you forget to come back to it or
you get busy or you feel like you kind
of have like squeezed the towel as dry
as you could at that point, right? And
so I think that AI allows us to squeeze
more out of that and get done more in
less time. So I think that like
basically the little nuggets or niches
or scope that we find or the bugs that
we oh and there are so many things that
I found in the past that I would have
not been able to then finish. like I
would have found leads in the past and
not been able to finish them that I can
now finish because of AI too. So I think
that um we're all kind of becoming
superheroes, you know, in some sense and
that will offset all of the negative
things that we just mentioned.
>> Yeah, 100%. And like you do have to
appreciate as well, you do have to build
somewhat of a different skill set to the
one that you're used to building. Before
it was very much okay just get the
fundamentals or look at whatever bug
class you're looking at and get really
good at that. Now it's a mix of managing
context, learning how to build a good
skill file, learning how to manage the
insane amounts of like output that's
generated from some of these things. And
then also learning how to get that in a
format where you can look at it and go,
"Okay, yeah, that's valid. That's a
gadget. That isn't. That's not." So, I
agree, but it's definitely you have to
learn how to use it properly, otherwise
you'll just be in the pit and cycle of
lots of noise, lots of junk, not being
effective.
>> Yeah. And so, um, you mentioned that
hacken proof thing as like a way to
potentially kind of fix this with, you
know, maybe like payon submission or
token submission required in order to
like cut down on the noise. Another
really nice way, well actually sorry,
there's two things here. One, I'll let
you mention what a couple companies have
done already around like screenshots and
videos.
>> Yeah. So there's been some programs
especially in some live events as well
basically asking you to like start your
submission with a screenshot or video to
help them ensure that what you are
submitting is actually valid and is not
AI slop because you have the proof or
the P or whatever it might be that you
actually have done the work and it is a
valid finding which I think is quite an
interesting and effective thing to do.
>> Yeah. And this this actually whenever
you mentioned that made me really think
about what Justin said. Justin mentioned
uh to me like maybe in like a chat or
something or maybe he posted on the
critical thinkers like uh a video first
or video only kind of like bug bounty
program. I don't love that uh at large
because I think that there's a lot of
times that I just would not do that for
a lot of bugs that I'm currently
submitting. But I do think that it
should be like a fast track um or you
know like some sort of way it should it
should play a factor in whether a bug
gets accepted and triage and like in the
order it gets triaged in and all of that
like I think that very often a
screenshot some screenshots and like a
video massively increase the validity of
a submission right because the triager
isn't necessarily guessing you know of
course you can forge screenshots or
forge videos but that's a lot of work
and then yeah I assume the platform
would kick you off if they caught you
doing that, like intercepting requests
or something to like fake a video.
>> And so I think um I think that programs
before they close shop, if they did want
to reduce the volume, they could do
something like that, like video
required, right? The same way the same
way you could do like dollar value
required or whatever.
>> I feel like that's a fair point. And in
all honesty, if I and I do this on most
of my submissions, but obviously
sometimes you get lazy. If you did make
a video pinging like for every
submission,
you would be protected start to finish
for every finding for when because
here's the other thing as well which is
like frustrating but understandable
>> is that there's now some cases where the
point from like triage to validation to
it being passed in internal teams the
bug is no longer reproducible or just
doesn't exist for one reason or another.
Yeah.
>> And it's like
I didn't make it up. You validated it at
the time. Like it was definitely real
and you confirmed that as well. But I
feel like it would also help that
because that has gotten me out of this
exact scenario a few times where they
go, "Okay, fair enough. You've got a
video PC like we'll honor it type
thing." So initially it would be a pain,
but once you get used to that flow and
you actually see a return on the benefit
of doing that, I feel like it would be
quite a good idea.
Yeah, I think that's actually great
feedback for the platforms. I was
thinking this whole time I think this
entire episode would be great for
platform uh for program owners and and
platform um you know customer success
managers and and product people to
listen to. But I think that's actually a
really great point that and and I think
it maybe until the validation and triage
times come down. I wish that the
platforms would add that as a standard.
Like basically if the bug hunter
invested time in your program to find a
vulnerability and they found a
vulnerability and they videoed it and
submitted it, like so what if you fixed
it in the meantime? Like that's not
their fault because then like it
literally incentivizes waiting longer in
hopes that just like some new feature
fixes it or that your internal team
finds it, you know, like
um it would be really great if that was
a standard where it's like, you know, it
still needs to be paid if it's videoed.
And like you said, a lot of hunters do
this anyway just to protect themselves
for any like, you know, higher critical
bugs to make sure they get it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean, it's only benefits.
It's just extra work really, which
>> to be honest with the current like
economy and state of things. I don't
actually mind if that becomes a thing
really. I like I think that's fair
enough. It's um it helps both sides. So,
please do that platforms.
>> All right, dude. Let's have this uh
training data debate.
>> Yeah. Okay, cool. So, one thing that I'm
conscious of and not a fan of right now
is
there's obviously you've got like um
what's it like hacker one brain MCP?
What what's the name of that project
when it can you can hook in hacker one?
>> Yeah, it's H1 brain, right? It's by
Yeah,
>> that's the one. Um, and you can hand it
over and a lot of hunters are actively
doing this to convert all their reports
into usable skills so they can get going
um, and get hunting straight away with
skills already created from previous
work they've done. Fair enough. One
thing I'm not in love with and one thing
I'm conscious of is that when you're
doing that, you're train you're you're
passing over all of your reports to
model providers which then gets thrown
into like the big pot of training data
which I feel like is kind of like
you're shooting yourself in the foot
long term. I feel like because
especially with the Claude uh security
release as well, I just feel like okay
well if I put what four 500 whatever it
is reports into Claude and that then
gets categorized and uses training data
then the model provider also has all of
my stuff and all my research or whatever
as well as the platform. So I'm not a
fan of that but you don't really seem to
>> yeah mind multiple things. one, it's
over anyways, you know, like it's
already over, but but like let's let's
say you don't think it's over and I
would just push back on a couple of
things. One, do you have training data
disabled? Like do you have you disabled
the the optin?
>> So, I've actually done two things here
on my personal one, I did disable it.
And second of all,
>> if you have an organization on these
platforms, like you actually buy an
organization and have your licenses
assigned for an organization,
>> you're not used for training data
>> that you're you're out of that.
>> Y
>> so I have an organization which I I use
to help prevent that as well,
>> right? So So I that kind of like puts
away the worries, right? But I think
that I've heard that in claude code that
that is like not as valid. Did you
research that?
>> What what what do you mean
>> that basically if you're using cloud
code you have to like go in and opt out
again basically like kind of like maybe
even per machine like there's like some
sort of settings file. So like if you
are like dynamically installing cloud
code on like a new on like VPS or you're
spinning up or you're scaling or you're
running on multiple places, you actually
have to go and disable the training data
across all of those.
>> All right. No, I didn't know that. But I
>> I think that's the case. Um but anyways,
let me let me push back a little more.
One is I think there are two things. Not
everyone is going to buy an
organization.
>> Mhm.
>> Right.
>> Agreed.
>> And like I'm sorry by not everyone I
mean not all bug hunters. Not not all
top one. Let's assume that all the
information from the bottom like two
like the bottom like if you're not in
the top 10,00 you've got no secret
skills. Even the top 10,000 bug hunters
are not going to all remember or go in
or disable that or buy an organization,
right? So they're already probably
slurping up lots of extremely high
quality data. And it doesn't take an
absurd number of samples. Like all it
takes is like a couple users. the I this
is probably why the tokens are so
subsidized, but with one Cloud Max
subscription, I mean, you can generate
hundreds of millions of tokens every
week or every month, right? And if they
have high quality skills and they're
running it on like hardened targets like
we are for Bug Bounty, that that those
session logs are extremely high quality
training data because the models today
are so good. So basically even if they
didn't generate synthetic data
internally which I think they are it
would still it would still be plenty of
training data just from the people who
forget to buy an or forget to turn it
off. But then furthermore, I think that
personally
the there are there are so many
extremely intelligent people at these
companies and they have so much money to
throw around with buying stuff from
third parties that I think it's
extremely likely they have some of the
best cyber evaluations even for appsac
you know that that look exactly like bug
bounty hunting and they're probably
running it on their own infrastructure
internally as well that my intuition is
that even if they had no user data they
would be able to basically heel climb
which they do anyways for all evals
right and right now not only do they
have cyberbench as like a base eval expo
has published you know eval open source
lots of other companies have I think
they can just develop their own evals
internally but furthermore when I was at
um I don't remember the name of the
conference there was a San Diego AI oh
offensive AI con it's like oicon it was
in San Diego like last year or something
Um the there were people from all the
top companies Meta, Google, Anthropic,
OpenAI and there was many there was a
couple talks that all implored the
audience. So these are all people who
are experts in security and AI and I
mean like actual experts not like
armchair experts. They implored them to
basically create more cyber data sets
and more cyber evals. Many of them did.
They went on to do that. And so I think
it's very likely that one these
companies did internally. two, they're
buying these data sets and they're
buying these evals from these thirdparty
people who are providing it or selling
it. And we're just going to see continue
massive improvement for cyber
capabilities in these models. And so
even if they had no user sessions, I
still think the models would continue to
improve. My point behind all that,
Brandon, is that I don't think you
personally putting in your reports
changes the outcome of the improvement
of these models at all or their ability
to release a product that will put us
out of business.
No, I do agree with what you're saying,
but get it's almost like the old like
privacy argument of like, oh, why do you
care about privacy if you got nothing to
hide? Blah blah blah. It's more it's
more the principle of you are putting
actively putting in your reports and
handing it over to another third party
>> which can be you like and
>> here's the thing as well like
>> I guess it would be more applicable for
like actual exploit researchers and
things like that but regardless
>> we're in this middle phase where right
now it's sort of like a free-for-all.
You can do that if you want. What's
interesting is that there's no been no
like policies put out by any of the
platforms to say like you can or can't
do this or things like that because
technically you are handing that over to
a third party right which is outside of
you the platform and the program
manager. So I don't know if there's
going to be changes there.
>> My point is and I'm coming at this I'll
be honest if I could self-host
everything I would like everything but
there's just too much work in that. I
would be much more comfortable in not
doing that or at least having some
protections around that because it's
just like you just feel like you're
adding to that inevitability of like
just do you see what I'm saying? Like
>> so I I agree with
>> I'm contributing to this.
>> Yeah, I agree with you on the privacy
front. It feels like that to me. I think
the analogy you're looking for is also
voting. Do you all do you all vote in
England or is this just a USA thing?
What
>> you all are a monarchy, right?
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah. We vote of course.
>> Yeah, I'm just joking. Yeah, I So, you
know, in obviously my single vote
doesn't matter at all,
>> right, to to any election. There's never
been an election decided by my vote, but
the act of voting is very important,
right? And like taking it to heart and
taking it seriously and exercising it in
that way is important. And I think
that's what you're saying, right? It's
like your individual reports don't
matter, but at large, you don't want to
contribute to the problem. And so I and
so I think that what I would say is that
>> there's a time to stand on principles
and there's a time to um do like a
riskreward analysis.
U well actually sorry you should always
be doing both those things. You should
be deciding what you want to stand on
principles and you should also be always
doing a riskreward analysis. And I think
for the vast majority of people and for
me personally, the risk versus reward
of, you know, using my reports as
um improvements to my Hackbot system.
Actually, I I've actually never I don't
think I've ever used my reports to
improve my system actually. But anyways,
I think if you want to do that, the
riskreward there is heavily on the
reward side because I think the the risk
of it changing the outcomes that are
going to happen are near zero. And I
think the rewards are that you find more
bugs. And if you found like one $5,000
bug or 10,000 bug on that, I think that
that's probably more more net value than
you would get from holding back and
trying to not contribute to the problem.
Um, but I think every person has to live
by their own standard of of what they
basically every person needs to live by
the uh live to the standard that they
believe in and that they want to like
hold themselves to. So if people don't
want to, I think that's totally
reasonable.
Yeah. And it the thing is as well like
as I said we're in this gray area where
policy and programs aren't covering this
yet. I don't know maybe I foresee some
changes around that happening. Um
because it kind of makes sense right you
are technically handing that over into
into another
>> third party which is completely it's its
own thing. It hasn't signed or agreed to
anything. Um, but I would say I'm very
much on the side of if I could self-host
everything I would, but I can't
obviously.
>> Um, and I very much am on the side of
caution like around those things. Is it
>> Let me give let me give you another
point in in your favor.
>> Go.
>> I think that
everyone in security knows this, but
there are plenty of people that don't.
And so maybe there's some listeners that
have never thought about this. They
probably have, but at every company
there are administrators that have
access to all the data. There there is
someone at Google that can just straight
up log in. They can just log into the to
the uh to the server, straight up dump
the DB of all of your emails, right?
Like we know this exists because all of
us have worked at companies and there
are administrators with access to
everything, right? Like that's that's
true at Meta and I'm sure it's true at
Anthropic, right? There's somebody
Anthropic that has the keys of the
kingdom that can read all the sessions.
And to be honest, I trust Google's
isolation and um permissioning because
they've had to iterate on this and
they've held sensitive data for decades.
And I'm sure that they are very anal and
uh have very extreme logging and um a
lot of checks and balances for who has
access to that data and when they access
it, where's their audit log, blah blah
blah. Whereas these startups like open
anthropics sometimes feel like they're
flying by the seat of their pants. So,
is there a China or North Korean plant
at these companies that is just saving
off all the session data that goes in or
whatever? It's like it's not out of the
realm of possibility. I don't think it's
very likely, but I don't I do think that
as a security person who needs to be
skeptical and needs to think about these
things, it is reasonable.
It's at least rational to be like mildly
worried that somebody will have access
to everything that you put into these AI
systems.
>> Yeah, exactly. just I'm I would
obviously I'm more on the cautious side
of it because that's just where I stand
on but like it's the same thing if you
paste an API key into like one of these
chats it tells you like nah like you
need to rotate this straight away now on
some model providers so it's the same
argument there but I know as you said
there's a lot of hunters that have done
it made skills like speedrun that
initial revision loop and they're
killing it. So,
>> yep.
>> I guess it's up to the individual.
>> Yeah. All right. Well, I we both been on
here for a while. We started late cuz we
were discussing it. Um, so yeah, for
anyone who stuck around again, if you
have any feedback,
forums.ctb.show/futurebugbounty.
All of those are underscored. So,
future_of_bug_bounty.
Give us some thoughts. Uh if you have
any ideas, if you do think this would be
super beneficial for programs or
platforms, feel free to you know tell
them to listen. I think um you know the
kind of TLDDR of all of this is that to
me it feels like there's a there's a lot
of network effects that make it
impossible to predict, but there are a
lot of negative ones. And so I think
people should, you know, personally I
think this year's kind of a cash grab
and Bug Bunny is going to get really
really hard by by sometime next year.
But I think there is a lot of copium
around being able to scale, being able
to find more than ever, being able to um
learn faster than ever and do more than
ever. Um it does kind of pain me that it
makes Bug Bounty more of a of a
lifestyle and less of a hobby, you know?
I think to to really thrive, you have to
eat and breathe it right now. And that
kind of sucks for people who just like
want to dabble in it. Like it's it's
going to be really hard to be a dabbler.
Yeah, I agree. And I think that's as
well again going to change like that
funnel of people that you have coming
into bug bounty. The people that stay,
the people that drop out as well. So it
is exactly as you say going to have more
downstream effects than we can possibly
predict or threat model on this call.
>> All right. Well, you got anything else,
Brandon?
>> No, that's it. We've covered the the
doom and gloom and theopium. I think
we've done we've ticked everything off
on the list.
>> Perfect. Thanks guys for tuning in. See
y'all. Peace.
>> And that's a wrap on this episode of
Critical Thinking. Thanks so much for
watching to the end, y'all. If you want
more critical thinking content, uh, or
if you want to support the show, head
over to ctv.show/isord.
You can hop in the community. There's
lots of great highlevel hacking
discussion happening there on top of
master classes, hackalongs, exclusive
content, and a full-time hunter guild if
you're a full-time hunter. It's a great
time. Trust me. All right, I'll see you
there.